Dinner time. Dinner time. Dinner time. Everybody. Dinner time. Let's have a quick conversation
about discernment. Okay. Because I really find that we've really got ourselves in quite
a pickle when we do not seem to consider discernment an example of intellect, but more so an indicator
of deceit. And that really is by design. Okay. Like you have been trained to do that. Come
on. No, no. You're over here, baby. You have been trained. Literally. You have been trained
to not consider discernment something that you should do so that it is easier for you
to be played with. That's what I'm trying to tell y'all. Like the discernment is something
that we got to get better at because also discernment is representational of not just your research
skill, but also of your intuition. And in order for your intuition to be moving at its
most pure, you have to be able to think without fear, but to think with clarity, to listen with
clarity. Right? Come here, baby. So you got to be able to connect. No, this is yours right
here. Why are you arguing with me? You got to be able to connect and discernment requires
questions and you have to ask questions. So you have to become practiced at asking questions
of yourself first. Okay. You've got to become good at asking questions. And when I say good,
I mean, it's fearless, fearless. You have to become fearless about asking yourself questions
because that's the thing. Some of y'all won't ask yourself certain questions because you're afraid
of the answer. I have five cats. Some of y'all are afraid to ask yourself questions. Why are you
eating his? You just gobbled up all of yours. Let him eat. Let him cook. You know? Oh, no one's
stressing me out. I'm just coming on here to speak to the people. And so discernment is a gift.
And it's a gift that you have. It's a sixth sense, but you have to train it. Okay. It's not
something that just happens because you have been trained not to use it. You have been trained
really not to exist in your body because discernment is so much about energy. And we've been trained not
to trust energy. We've been trained to not even think energy is a real thing. We've been trained
to think that energy is some woo-woo fake corny shit when really energy is one of the realest
things out here. Frequency is a real thing. You can see it. Frequency is not some made-up
thing. Okay. So you got to train. You got to train yourself out of the numbness. We have
been trained to be numb. We have been trained to not believe, to not trust, to not feel. So
we've got to train ourselves to listen and to feel. We've got to really understand the
way our bodies function. You know, the different functionalities of our body all do different
things. And when you get to the bottom of it, when you see the connectivity, you're like,
all of them require energy and movement. So, you know, I want to just inspire you all to,
um, Lumumba, why you be trying to eat everybody else's food? You ate all your food and now you're
trying to get up on everybody else. Let them, this is the culprit. This is the culprit, Lumumba.
Everybody is trying to just eat their food in peace. And Lumumba is like, nah, but can I get
some? Um, and so what I also want to, to say is that when you are skeptical, when you are skeptical,
um, in an honest, pure way, no one should be offended by that. No true person should be offended
by that. And that is one of the easiest measures of finding out who's on what, on what type of time.
Who's on what type of time, right? Because someone here said literally living in a self-abandonment
epidemic, 1000%, which is why we have to train ourselves to be back in touch with ourselves.
So like one of the things that I've been doing, and I've been talking to my Patreon community about
this is I get up every day and I do 20 minutes of some kind of movement. I either swim, I do yoga,
I do, I I'll do like a circuit of like sit-ups and, and, um, pushups and those things, um, and those
things. And then I'll do, or I'll do, um, I'll do, uh, Tai Chi, um, or I'll just dance.
I used to know my human design, but I always forget it. Um, so anywho, what I'm saying to
those who are listening to what I'm actually saying, cause some of y'all aren't paying any
attention, but the, the, the work of getting back into your body will allow you to be able to have
better discernment about who's around you, about who's considering themselves help about who, about
if you're, how you're being surveilled and where you're being surveilled. And, you know, all of
these things are necessary because the powers that be, they, they have the same access to power as
you. They've just prevented you from having access to that power. They've been spending centuries
taking the power of the earth and turning it into weapons. And so you now have to consciously
identify that power of the earth and turn it into, uh, and reconnect it to you.
You are a revolution. All of us, all of us, we are all a revolution individually because our bodies
have been weaponized against us, which means that we can take control of them. If they have been a
useful weapon for the, for the, for those trying to harm us, then we can take control of them and make
them weapons that we are in control of. And a weapon does not need to be seen as something that is
negative. In my opinion, a weapon is something that protects, right? A weapon is something that,
uh, forces discernment, right? And what better to protect than the earth? So here's the thing,
Joel seven, the powers that be are watching this. They can, they can take notes. There's no, there's
no, the beauty of surveillance is realizing that if y'all can see everything, if everything is
connected, then everything is connected. If everything is connected, then everything is
connected, not just the negative. And I want you to remember that when you feel overwhelmed,
when you feel like the powers are too powerful, when you feel like they are raining down upon us in a
manner in which we cannot fight back, remember everything is connected.